{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Enterprise Architecture",
    "Term": "Finals",
    "Title": "Finals Reviewer",
    "LastModified": "15 December 2024",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "Finals Reviewer"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "This modeling action can be done by adding specific details to existing elements",
      "answer": "Refinement",
      "choices": [
        "Refinement",
        "Risk analysis",
        "Internal Drivers",
        "Use of colors"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Example of these are regulatory framework and government laws",
      "answer": "External Driver",
      "choices": [
        "External Driver",
        "Application association viewpoint",
        "Private business process",
        "Application usage viewpoint"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This viewpoint depicts the relationships of applications in a company, including the dependencies in terms of the services a company offers",
      "answer": "Application association viewpoint",
      "choices": [
        "Application association viewpoint",
        "Business function viewpoints",
        "Model-Driven Architecture",
        "Deployment diagram"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This process helps architects to identify and manage potential problems that could arise within the project period",
      "answer": "Risk analysis",
      "choices": [
        "Risk analysis",
        "Refinement",
        "Internal Drivers",
        "Selecting viewpoints"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This type of business process modeling notation element includes sub-processes, loops, and compensation",
      "answer": "Activity",
      "choices": [
        "Activity",
        "Business function viewpoints",
        "Private business process",
        "Deployment diagram"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is a visual attribute that is strongly influenced by \"prior knowledge\"",
      "answer": "Use of colors",
      "choices": [
        "Use of colors",
        "External Driver",
        "Internal Drivers",
        "Application usage viewpoint"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It contains equipment such as machines, tools, and/or instruments that can create, use, store, move, or transform materials",
      "answer": "Physical viewpoint",
      "choices": [
        "Physical viewpoint",
        "Application usage viewpoint",
        "Business function viewpoints",
        "Selecting viewpoints"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It pertains to a viewpoint that describes how applications are used to support one (1) or more business processes",
      "answer": "Application usage viewpoint",
      "choices": [
        "Application usage viewpoint",
        "Physical viewpoint",
        "Business function viewpoints",
        "External Driver"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is a sub-model within a business process modeling notation diagram that involves internal processes to a specific organization and does not cross organizational boundaries",
      "answer": "Private business process",
      "choices": [
        "Private business process",
        "Activity",
        "Model-Driven Architecture",
        "Risk analysis"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is a structural unified modeling language diagram that depicts the physical resources in a system, including nodes, components, and connections",
      "answer": "Deployment diagram",
      "choices": [
        "Deployment diagram",
        "Business function viewpoints",
        "Internal Drivers",
        "Refinement"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It aims to provide an open and vendor-neutral approach to interoperability and raises the level of abstraction in enterprise architecture",
      "answer": "Model-Driven Architecture",
      "choices": [
        "Model-Driven Architecture",
        "Physical viewpoint",
        "Selecting viewpoints",
        "Risk analysis"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Examples of these are the mission and vision of an organization",
      "answer": "Internal Drivers",
      "choices": [
        "Internal Drivers",
        "Business function viewpoints",
        "Application association viewpoint",
        "Risk analysis"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It provides high-level insight into the general operations of the company, which is used to structure an organization according to its main activities",
      "answer": "Business function viewpoints",
      "choices": [
        "Business function viewpoints",
        "Model-Driven Architecture",
        "Application usage viewpoint",
        "Deployment diagram"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This serves as a guide in determining appropriate information to be included in a model",
      "answer": "Selecting viewpoints",
      "choices": [
        "Selecting viewpoints",
        "Refinement",
        "Activity",
        "Business function viewpoints"
      ],
      "reference": "Finals Reviewer",
      "term": "Finals"
    }
  ]
}